Yo, the veil is thin the mic is hot welcome to the show where the truth gets caught
Drama meets destiny cats on patrol tarot cards flit while we bear the soul spawns a steps up pays 10 opens the door
Then the panel pops off like never before from trolls to truthers witches and kings
Everybody's welcome. Just mind what you play
Chaos and tea, that's divine
Pull up your seat, you're right on time
You're right on time
From shadow work Saturdays to soul truth Sundays
Panel so packed, they're spilling out runways
Lenors on your shoulder, tricks got the vibe
Lola Rudy Marbles, it's a feline tribe
universe family messy and slick we go deep we go real we cast and reveal if the
cards don't scare you the trolls sure will
Yo, the veil is thin the mic is hot welcome to the show where the truth gets caught
Drama meets destiny cats on patrol tarot cards flip
Hi guys take two one second
Okay, nevermind
How are you guys doing? Let's see, it's freezing. Okay, are we okay?
Hello bot, HaloTron. Let's see, I have some coffee coming guys.
What's up? Do you hear me now? Oh, shoot.
Do you hear me now? Yes, I'm back. Hello. Okay guys, how are you doing today?
Are you able to hear the song? I tried to book a guest today, but I overslept a little bit,
so I think I missed him today, but I think he'll come back.
Gonna see yeah, it's actually like this big bodybuilder guy
Hope he comes by sometime I told him I try to get back by on four o'clock, but it's five o'clock here now
I just woke up
You're gonna see tricks. Well, there's Lola miss Lola's over there. Hey Lola
Lola the alien cat
Okay, I'm Mikey
I was just able to get a couple copies.
They have a deal on DoorDash for 40% off on two orders
if you use Cash App.
I had a little bit on Cash App, so.
Got some coffee. I have my leftovers from last night. Hey guys. How are you?
I got also got some two new decks of cards today in the mail
I got the believe in your own magic oracle deck looks cool
Can't wait to pull some cards from that and also what is this deck?
This is the celestial carnival tarot. I mean it looks I like the colors actually it does look a little bit faded
I think these are probably
Maybe
I never share, I said I keep the food, yeah.
Well, Starbucks is pretty good.
Thank you, so I can't wait to pull these out
and cut these on Timu.
You can get some good deals,
I don't necessarily know if these are the original deck,
but let me have a look at these cards.
They look like they're good quality.
That's what they look like in the back, a couple back cards I guess.
Milkshake look good, yeah. Okay, and it starts out here's a fool.
I'm working also on my deck. I got a couple new cards today.
I don't know if I saved them yet. Let me see if I can show them.
Well, here's one of them.
I got the magician I saved but I forgot to save the other one. Let's see the magician though.
Do you like that style? It's kind of cartoonish, mystical style.
Looks a little bit more like me. Cartoon version of me, of course. I hear tricks.
I will be adding like some things to like the community board. It looks like you Baldwin
Okay, the big bodybuilder guy is here, okay, hold on a second
Here's a link this is just for him right now guys
I'll do a reading for him if you'd like
Welcome, thank you for coming. I'm sorry. I'm a little bit late. It is 504 here, but
The chat is kind of excited got 24 people in chat already
Yeah guys, okay, and so let's see and we want to get his
His like can a mod please post his link
Had got some
I have copies here's a small one. Yeah
First come on tricks over here tricks clear
Are we gonna show tricks? I need to grab my coffee to my coffee door. I think a plurty diamond
Kit mr. Trixie your back in my coffee real quick. Let's get into this let's get into this
Not here yet
Not here yet. Okay, they scare him away. Hopefully I didn't scare him away. Okay
You can figure out the link a flirty diamond. How are you? Maybe we'll get auto back tonight. Have you had any auto experiences?
That was odd yesterday. It wasn't it
We had auto auto is having some
Some fun on my show I think Slayer what's up guys
Nice to meet you. Well, I don't know if Daddy Bigness is able to figure out the
StreamYard
But if not, I still want to support his channel. So
Can a mod please post his link?
Just click on his name
Then copy his channel. You know, you had to share his channel
It was inspired by you since he likes transformers.
You have its issues, let me see.
Hi, guys.
Otto, are you here?
I'm wondering if Otto is here today.
Here we got the cats up here, kitty cat, Trixie, Trix got Lola over there.
Okay, well I guess anybody can come up on the link then.
Hopefully he didn't get scared to run away. Maybe hopefully
Technical difficulties will be able to arrange that soon if it's not working their work today, but thank you for coming though. Appreciate that
Okay, so anyway 15 minutes already all crazy
Mr. Otto is here not yet. I haven't seen him yet, but I think Otto will appear
Like yesterday
Say his name. I've already said his name three times Otto
Try to figure out how okay you go um
you click on the link and
Then it should just say like
Check your camera as long as you have your camera
Microphone you can do it from your cell phone. You can do it from computer
Just click on the link.
Type in your name that you want to have displayed on the screen.
And then it should say go live or something.
But we're good.
I still have to grab my coffee from the door.
So no rush.
Thank you for coming, by the way.
So guys, he's a really cool guy.
He's like, he has a couple of these voices.
He talks about where to stop the app.
I'll grab my coffee, and we'll get started.
OK?
I don't want to give away too much here got my coffee real quick
and if anyone has advice for getting it on the stream yard
once uh you do like have your camera working it will say
you'll top up on my screen i'll really bring you up and you'll be on my split screen
this is good because because of your first your first interview or your first appearance hi
so is that ucig is that ujip drinking off backstage i think i saw ucig right
Were you under the name Tom Flash?
Tato had Harry. Did Flirty beg for those pictures? I haven't seen it on my Discord yet.
Was that just now, Sig? When was that?
Harry but jokes are hot. Oh, wow. Harry but whole jokes. Oh
Yeah, but so one of the things I like to do is find talented people on YouTube
This guy's definitely very oh here we go
Hello
Hello, can you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
Yeah, cool.
Thank you for being on the show.
How are you today?
Well, thanks for having me.
Oh, you're very welcome.
So, OK, so go ahead and tell us about your channel
and what you do on YouTube.
Well, I just played a lot of college.
Well, I played one college, Florida played soccer.
Played a lot of sports growing up.
Kind of like an athlete at heart so I had to continue something. So I started getting into the gym
I figured out I was actually pretty good at it. So I just took it as far as I can
Okay wise
How much do you weigh?
Right now probably like 225
Okay, you know, how tall are you?
Only like 58 maybe 59 on a good day
Okay, well, I'm six three. I'm like a hundred and fifty pounds
Yeah, I was like a hundred and thirty five pounds like five years ago when I was running around playing soccer a lot
When I ate a bunch of protein and freakin McChickens and McDoubles and try to get as big as possible
Okay, he did the McDonald's McDonald's diet route
So you seem to have like a kind of it you have a kind of a character when you work out or at least you like you
It sounded like I thought you were maybe schizophrenic when I first started watching you
You have a character who's your care? Who's your who's your alter ego or your?
Yeah
Yeah, okay, we have it we have somebody that wants to come on with you hold on do you mind if I bring a guest on
Okay, oh one second
Hey Trevor, let's take it. Sorry. Hold on. Let's take it. I muted you accidentally Trevor
Hi, you guys, how are you doing? I see you got any guests on I'll just hang out in the background here
I'll let you guys talk and then
And then I'll I'll come on. Okay guys have a head your conversation. So okay. Thank you
Trevor good to see you site good to see you
You too. Okay. Look look a daddy big does
Ever everyone knows is a special guest today, so yeah
So I want everyone to check out daddy bigness's channel too a lot of people on here that would like to
Come in and say hi to you. I'm sure in your chat. So if a mod can post his his chat
But you so you've been working out
Like I guess bulking. I guess it's a term like for the past few years
Yeah, I've been doing a lot of powerlifting
How'd you get really into that because it sounds like you were like probably about my my weight and then uh
Yeah, it's pretty small. Well, I don't know. I just uh
Started going to gym. I thought it's smaller right and I'm a little shorter, so
I just felt like I had to do something to be a little bit more physically imposing I guess
But that's not really the point like the point is I hate confrontations and my goal is to get so big so strong that you know
I don't have to deal with that
but
No, I'm a nice guy
How old are you if you ask me asking how old are you? I just turned 26
Oh, you're okay. You're fairly young. So
So you feel like you want to get
You want you want to build your strengths is what you're saying by working out and
All that good stuff
Yeah, that's basically what I do any powerlifting. So that's kind of like where you worry about how much you can list
Not like what you look like
How much cool how much do you bench like so you do like a bench, but you do like what like a one at a time sometimes
Where are you from you're from Missouri you said I think I'm sorry from Maryland Maryland, okay, so if anybody in the chat is from Maryland shout out
But this is a really he's a really he's a really good guy and you got married recently didn't you yeah like a month ago
Okay, congratulations. I saw some of your wedding photos. Yeah, he's married. Oh
How old is your if you don't mind me asking how old is your wife your 26 said she's about to be 27
Oh
Bad bit a tad bit older than you okay, how did you uh if you don't because you just I mean 20s to me
I'm 37 26 seems uh, so young to me
But uh, how did you two meet if you don't mind me asking? Well, we met in college
So we've known each other for like almost eight years now
Wow
Yeah, but the spikes look looking at me like oh this idiot's trying to take over. No, no, no, no, I know I like it actually
So yeah, go ahead
You do your thing buddy. I
Know but it's funny because it's like, you know, I think I've probably I've probably flirted with him a little bit
I've never tried to you know, but he did it well. He took it. He took it. He took it in stride
I was and I just like to see how people react sometimes, but
It is like, oh no, I got I got a bunch of gay guys in the chat
Teresie's funny. I've been doing my show for about
About six months or seven months just to doing the open panels and maybe ten months having the show
And so it's pretty went pretty well. I really think that
Fitness is a good genre on YouTube and I I think you should have more people in your chat
And so hopefully some people in my chat will go say hi to you because you you do like it be several times a week
You do some lifting right on on stream
Yeah, I'm not live streaming. I started my channel. This is like I don't like the right stuff down
So it's kind of like my journal and now it's like visual so I can go back and see exactly what I did
But I'll just live stream anybody can join it gets a little crazy in there sometimes
Once it's all over, okay. I'll sigh sigh relief
Yeah
Well, it's really it's really it's a thrill to talk to you
And I do enjoy your channel a lot
I think, you know, you have a good positive message, I guess, um, and I
You can see it that way if you look at it correctly
Like I got there's your channel up there. So I hope everyone subscribes. Hopefully you get some new subscribers
So I know you you had to get to at least 50. How is that process to get to your be able to start live streaming? I
Didn't get to 50. I didn't even know that I
Was that like something recent?
I don't know
When I first tried to go live like I first made my channel
It was like all you have to wait 48 hours before you can do your first live stream or whatever
That's all I was I didn't really need any certain number of subscribers. Oh cool. When did you start your channel? Oh?
Maybe like like three years ago like three october's ago. Maybe okay. I don't know. Yeah
Well, they have it now now is that I think you need maybe need a hundred subscribers now or something like 50 to 100
It was 50 when I started
Now a hundred, but yeah, you got in you got in earlier. So
Do you ever want to you ever had dreams about monetizing your channel or your channel growing or you know somehow?
You know you go viral for something. Well, yeah, I think
Well, maybe not everybody I think most people on the internet. That's one of the main factors
Wasn't really for me, but if it happens, that's cool. I just I like to
Share my journey and if I can help people achieve their goals, I'd be cool
It would be my dream job being a quote-unquote fitness influencer
I don't know
I don't know. I'd be the more like a motivational person probably because people probably aren't gonna want to do exactly what i'm doing
Yeah, I would say throw in some of the motivational talk into your if your videos
I think that would be a great a great way to connect with people more
We have people already interested. Do you have an only fans we hear in the chat?
I don't think he does because I would have found it but what it was
No
Okay, he's a little bit more conservative, but you know, he does like to
He will get you did you damn flex a couple of times for me. I think by request
It's pretty it's pretty
Impressive, okay, we might have a porn bomber. Let me I'm not gonna let this person out
I don't want to ruin my interview with you
That is one of the hazards of
I'm doing live streams. I bring people on and sometimes there's a porn bomb and I have to delete delete the stream
You know
They'll put porno up when I bring them on so I know you I know you you're a good guy
And so have you flipped some tires before we have Nick here
He's that kind of a he likes to come on and flip some tires and do some yard work in his
shorts
Think about doing some yard work out there. I don't know. That's what Nick has started to do
He said have you flipped tires before though?
I don't think I've ever flipped any tires before. I'm sure I can I just that's not really what I do
Nick has flipped some tractor tires. Well, just some ideas. I got five cats. Do you have any pets?
Yeah, I have one dog
Kind of dog do you got?
German shipper shepherd mix
Very nice here. Trevor's coming back. I think Trevor wants some more questions
Go on Trevor. Oh
My god, I'm sorry. I'm sorry psych. I'm just such a complete fricking catastrophe
I'm such a burden on your channel's shoulders, and I apologize about that, but
But so so what are we talking about? What's the conversation? What are we talking about?
We're talking about different things he does on the show. We're talking about Nick Johnson for a second
I had you know, Nick asked if he flipped some tractor tractor tires, but have you got any questions?
So my god, I
26 years old being married, you know what my
My parents were 24 years. I'm 37 now. My parents were 24
When they had me and I can't they weren't married by the way, they were not married by any means, but
Yeah, I can't even imagine like
Even at 37 even the kid thing getting married, but I
mean
So so everything
How's marriage going?
It's going well. We've only been married for like a month.
But it's good.
Oh, like a month's okay.
Oh, okay.
Really?
Very nice.
Are you planning on having kids soon?
Yeah, probably within like a year.
Probably.
You know what? Hey pal, I would give it a little bit more than a year because
God-willing God-willing you and your wife are married for 30, you know until the end of time God-willing
But if you have kids and then something doesn't work out, I mean you're I hate to say it
I hate to say it. You're you're you're on the hook for those kids
I only know that a long time
I don't know what you're saying, but sometimes you just got to go for it, you don't want to plan to fail.
Fair enough, fair enough. I get it, I get it.
Yeah, well if anyone else has a question, I mean, I just wanted to like make sure like that
I think you're a really great, uh, you're a great streamer
I have an entertaining show and I really wanted to like just help you out
Get maybe get a few more subscribers and put yourself out there a little bit more
Thanks, I think you have a great message. I subscribe. So look forward to me in your chat
It gets a it gets a little rough in there sometimes or just get people ahead. Oh, you can't be any rough and then uh
Then what what site deals with and you're right? Yeah, I got a pretty crazy show
Yes, and we have a Yumi cat on to say hi we have a nice female if you have a female, okay, here you go
Hi
Hi friends. Hi new friends
This is Yumi. Yumi's in Indonesia, so we have worldwide people here. Say hi to Daddy Bigness.
You have to just call me Andrew if you want. Okay, okay, Andrew.
Okay, Andrew, okay. I hope you're doing well, Mr. Psyche. Thank you. Someone's from the chat.
Someone from the chat saying that you look like someone for us. You look not okay. I hope you're doing a song for us, Psyche.
Do you think it's on?
She did
Guys, I'm watching daddy big news or I'm watching Andrew now and he's gonna be helping me
I'm gonna watch him. He's gonna help me bulk up. Okay. He's my motivation to like to look healthier
You know, I'm gonna get like big
You look fine. I like fine. Yeah, I look a little good to know
Get to know today. I'm gonna watch
tribe
Yes, I think everyone's excited ever. It's excited to try it like let's see
Yeah, we got a lot of a lot of people in the chat say hi everyone make sure to subscribe to daddy bigness
Hey, you mean you do sing songs were you on clicks panel singing songs before or am I thinking of a completely different person?
me
You mean he was singing you was singing. Yeah, you me was singing. I'm sorry
Yeah, you be safe. I cannot. I cannot think. Okay. Do you have a question for Daddy Bigness? You hear me? Sorry. For Andrew. For Andrew.
I don't know. I don't have any question. I just came to say hello. Okay. Well, thank you. Yeah, but this guy's a good guy, guys.
Everyone subscribed to his channel and thank you. I'm sorry. I know I was late. I fell asleep and I know you said at four o'clock, so I appreciate you coming. Yeah.
When's your next time you planning to go live, dude? Oh
Friday
That's just gonna be like a little bodybuilding day nothing crazy the crazy heavy weights are gonna go down or Monday
I'm gonna do bench press and then
Andrew I'll be there. I'll be there baby boy
Front and center. I wonder what you eat. What do you eat in an average day?
Like you are pretty big so when you started bulking like what's your what's your average meal a day?
So, I mean
Yeah, it's hard for me to stay this size because like naturally I'm not that big
but yeah, like
like when I wake up, I'll just
Usually eat like three or four oatmeal packets
And then I'll have a banana if I have them and then I'll hit my protein powder
and that's probably around like
Almost a thousand calories right when I get up probably like 40 grams of protein maybe
And then throughout the day before lunch, I'll snack. I'll probably eat like another thousand calories
Probably like another like 70 grams of protein and then lunchtime. I'll eat like 1500 calories some more protein
and then usually I work out after that and then I try to
Not eat until it's dinnertime after my workout, but like in a day. I probably eat like four or five thousand calories, maybe
Wow
I probably eat about
Go ahead. I'm sorry. I probably bet five times less than that, but go ahead Trevor
No, I was just gonna I was just gonna glow. I was gonna blow up my diet. I just uh earlier today
I had Tyson's Tyson's
frozen chicken nuggets just
Processed beyond belief and I'm sure it's just like just salt in the word trans fat
Man, I just scarf those bad boys down earlier just scarf them down
but uh
I'm not young and in my prime like Andrew is I wish I was but I'm not but uh
Have you ever enjoyed yourself a pop tart Andrew a pop tart?
Have ever ate one
Like yeah, yeah
No, so I I do powerlifting so like I don't care what I look like I am a little fat
I don't care about that. I just care about how much weight I could lift so I eat like a practice puzzle
I don't really care nice
Nice, that's what I'm talking about
That's well I
Well, I'm gonna I'm gonna be watching your streams now. What happened to you me hey
You left but I'm so sorry. Can I ask like is that the girl who was singing sweet child of mine?
She's like an agent that that's that that is a that's a Kona from the Philippines. You know
Completely confused
But you go ahead and talk I'll put on mute for a minute. Okay
Well, yeah, it's like, you know, I think
That eating healthy is
Something I really don't have to worry about because I need to gain all the weight. I can but
but yeah, Andrew you really do inspire and I
Hope that I helped you today
Make some a make some new fans and friends
but I just wanted to say hey to you and
Hopefully I'll help you back in the can have you back in the future
I don't want to keep you too long today, but I did want to just put yours put you out there and
Introduce myself, and I want to thank you very much for coming up here on the show, and I'll uh, I look forward to seeing you again
and
On your show and hopefully my show so
Okay, cool
Cool, did anyone else wants to come up on panel? Anyone else want to say anything? Yeah, so I also do tarot cards
I don't know if you're into tarot cards or completely against it, but I'd be happy to do a reading for you if you'd like
Okay, okay, I got some alien tarot cards right here
and
Look at a shuffle and see what I got for you. I'll do a nice tarot cards. He said they're alien
Oh, can we see them?
Can we get a vape?
Oh, those are not.
No, there's like one of them.
I like that too.
They glow in the dark.
They're kind of, they kind of have a beautiful bright colors.
I don't know if they're going in the dark,
but these are some cool cards.
You got all the tarot cards.
Yeah, I have almost 50 decks.
I've been doing tarot since I was like eight years old.
So let's get for daddy, for Andrew.
Let's see what we got.
Okay.
Okay, drop one. Okay, here we go. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Okay.
Okay, I see like you meet you. You have you have you have a lot of things a lot of things making you happy and everything
And I see that I see your wife, too
I see her she's coming up as a queen of cups like this. I don't know if she's a water sign, but she's a very a very
control of her emotions kind of person
But I think I see it like a lot of competition are almost like you maybe have some heads of competition for her at the beginning
Okay
And you're coming up as a king of swords and so you you definitely know
What you what you like and you don't like and are willing to cut things out of your life that don't serve you, okay?
let's see
We have the world card so you're coming to the end of a cycle and
Coming into a new cycle you've successfully completed it
And I see you working with some people to make some money
in the future, okay?
And I also see you, these are maybe people
that you party with or in your social network, okay?
What else do I have?
A couple more than some advice for you, okay?
Ten of wands it's like I see you ten of wands is like this this person's carrying a lot
And I know you do carry a lot physically and maybe mentally. I think you maybe carry a lot of
Maybe a motion's for other people too
The advice I have for you is to
Maybe work work up work with somebody one-on-one or and continue to maintain balance
And I see you you're a hard worker
Things are paying off for you, finally.
I see also, your wife is coming up as the Empress,
which is all the queens in the deck.
So it looks like you got a great woman, I would say.
Take good care of her and good luck in your relationship
and I wish you the very best.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I got so many in the chat today and I'm on Roids.
Andrew, why would I want my voice to be so high?
Andrew, forget about the...
I'm too fat for Roids.
That would be quite obvious.
Andrew, forget about the Roids.
Can we just hear your thoughts?
Your detailed thoughts on the tarot read that Christ has gave you?
Yeah, I think it's cool. I think some of it definitely is correct. He said you got a team good woman
That's what he said. I heard it said you got a good woman
So that's all right
I don't know if he's added to tarot, but you know, maybe maybe some stuff will resonate with you later
but I really I really do see good things happening for your channel and
Definitely increasing there, but keep going at it. I would say really she was often as you can. That's my advice
I'm now monetized on YouTube
And if you ever need any advice on monetization or any of that, I'm here for you.
Okay.
I'm happy to help you anytime I can.
Hey, Sike.
Yes.
That was a beautiful read.
Oh, thank you.
That was beautiful read.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad you liked it and he liked it.
See so BSBB says I've been a bigger all natural than juice. Okay. Yeah, I don't think
Okay
Okay, who's it come up here to do a flex off, you know, I wanted I wanted to do this
Come on join right away, please
My family actually didn't reflect off, not my fat ass, somebody else better come up here.
Not with a pretty decent old man, 37, not a chance.
Get up here, get up here, one of you young boys who are fit and in their prime.
Get up here now.
I think everyone's...
Everyone knows a daddy bigness of Andrew's gonna gonna win that contest and
Yeah, you're fine you're fine you're fine anybody maybe this person backstage wants to flex let's just check it out
Let me see I need to put it my baby
Anybody can pose I teach you how to do it right now
Okay Pedro are you there? Yeah, I'm still here
Got a new page. We got Pedro backstage or Pedro here. Oh
Here we go. Hold on. I'm gonna take him off and then put you on
Here we go
There we go
Look at this guy
You look like an incredible Hulk. Goddamn. Look at him.
I'm pretty strong.
Nice. Oh my God. Nice. Yeah. Yeah. Beautiful.
Yeah.
I'm so glad you're doing this without pre-workout.
What do you think, Chad?
Whoa.
You're there. Nice. Thank you.
That was great. You weren't kidding.
You're going to set up. Oh, wow. Well, that explains it. That explains it. Very nice.
You want to
There we go get off the camera
Thank you
Thank you for that
Can I ask Andrew a question real quick? Of course? Why do I be more like him and less like a?
Pathetic fat loser like me
any tips Angel
And go lift some heavy weights and call yourself a powerlifter
I'm talking baby stuff.
You can keep being fat.
Just call yourself a power worker.
That's what I did.
Oh, I got you.
No, you look good.
You look good.
You look really good.
You obviously put work into it and I've seen your setup there.
So, yeah, that's awesome.
That's awesome.
Good for you.
Thanks.
Yeah, and yeah, you are actually really really cool. He's really kind guys too. I know I like I love a good heart
You know and so of course that
I
Feel like he was doing those poses in honor of
Terry Balea ho Kogan himself like I felt
Tribute to the man
Oh
Don't do the Hulkster don't do
You just passed away a few days ago.
I know, he was only 71, that's what I'm saying, doing all those stairways. Heart can't keep up.
Well, from what I've, I mean, you're a young guy, you're 26, you don't have to worry about it, but
from everything that I've read, it's not good to...
Even that muscle when you're that age, especially in your 70s or 80s, it's not good to carry that muscle
You should be more
Thin than anything because it when you're that old it weighs on your heart even the weight from your muscles or
Whatever not, but the bigger you are the more blood your heart's gonna pump out
Well, you're a stud you are a
alien you're 26 you're in the prime of your life and
And dad you you're doing good very nice very nice. Congratulations
Congratulations young man
Yeah, you guys you got a lot going for him, you know
Newly wed and he's got a good channel going so I really want to support this guy and
Everyone make sure you go to daddy bigness's channel. You can he's really funny actually you will be entertained
And impressed I'm sure you will be he does lift up like four pounds at a time
I don't think you guys realize I got a big ass belly.
No, you haven't seen short and fat until you see me.
And you're not going to see me because I'm not
turning my camera on.
You haven't seen short and fat.
And he does have a great belly, and he does not mind showing it.
So if you guys are into bellies, you know.
Who me no, well, you know anybody if anybody's in the belly is you know, this is the guy that this is the guy to watch
She's got a she's got a great one. So
If I accidentally uh
For a brief second I accidentally showed myself on benny's stream. I accidentally
I tried to do the exit this stream
And I pushed the camera and meanwhile, I just like a fat piece of shit just no shirt on
and, uh, and yeah, it wasn't pretty, but, uh,
well, he's going to beat me.
He's going to beat me in the boxer ring now.
Watch some of, watch some of Andrew, uh, Andrew Trevor
and get inspired, right?
Get inspired to, then call yourself a power lifter.
And, uh, yeah.
Can you, can you lift a lot of weight, Trevor?
Fuck no
Like up until my 30s, I was a skinny young guy like I was really skinny
But I hit 30 I got on the I got on the Zoloft
I got on the Zoloft and I started drinking hard and before I knew it. I was a I
Was a short chubby man
It's Pedro there Pedro there
Yes, okay
Good to see you the question for our guests
Yes, what is the heaviest you can
for what lift like because I'm not very professional at this
Um
Like so so for powerlifting there's your three main lifts
Your bench pressing your deadlift and then like if you go to a meet you have three tries to put up the biggest number
And then you add them all up and then that's how they decide who wins
And it's all based off of weight classes and stuff like that
Now I don't do any of that crap, but my biggest bench press I said earlier was 405
My biggest squat was 500. I didn't really mess around with the squat too much and I just started deadlifting today
I actually hit six plates. That's five eighty five
Definitely gonna at least go to six hundred
Fuck maybe six seventy five seven place. Well, we'll see
More months, then I'm gonna start cutting someone's asking about personal training services. Do you do any of that you?
I'm going to FaceTime everybody and help anybody to see what they're trying to.
Okay.
Yeah, so I guess you can contact him.
He's very easy to talk to.
Go to his chat.
Go ahead.
Sorry, sorry.
You're fine.
The thing was, uh, what was I going to say?
Uh, what was I going to say?
Personal training?
With personal training?
Yeah, personal training.
I don't fucking remember, yeah, Mike.
I'm just, I just said if you, like, if you were interested in personal training, I think
he would help you out.
So just, I would say go to his chat, and he's very easy to talk to in there.
And maybe he'll give you his Snapchat or something.
Oh, yeah, that's what I was going to say, I was going to say, like...
The art of lifting whether your bodybuilding or powerlifting like the science behind it isn't that hard to understand
It's it's it's hard work to do it though
Right because if your bodybuilding you're either going to muscular failure where your arm doesn't fucking curl the thing anymore
So that's kind of mentally taxing or if you're powerlifting or getting in the mindset to murder somebody and with something really fucking heavy
but like
If you're gonna try to get strong, you should stay in your sets should be,
we're only able to lift that weight like three to five times. I'll be considered heavy weight
if you can only do it for three to five times. Do five sets of that, then you're a powerlifter.
If you're trying to do bodybuilding, you work to the pain like every time you try to go to failure
Try to get like 15 reps are better if you're doing body. Hey, Andrew Andrew if I can ask do you feel like
Starting off like maybe somebody who's not necessarily in shape. Do you feel like maybe cardio is better?
And then hitting the weights after that once they get their weight under control
Well, yeah, I feel like looking good and having abs and all that that's not about how many punches you do
That's about it's all calories and calories out. That's all in the kitchen kind of stuff
You're trying to lose weight. You should yeah, you should watch me eating
Try to do a little bit more cardio as long as you're eating less food
Then you're using an energy a day
Then you're doing good if you guys really want to know like you guys can listen to me
I only have like 400 subs like what do I know? But there's this guy called Greg you set
who is a professional powerlifting and bodybuilder and he knows all the nutrients facts and all that
but the thing is people think they have to starve themselves every day to lose weight you really
don't you know it's being like a couple hundred calorie deficit you won't really notice it you
All right. Well, hey psych. I'm gonna drop off Andrew
I'm I cannot wait to see you you're in the prime of your life. It's a prime of your life, and
And yeah, I can't I can't wait to watch your streams and your channel
So thanks for having me on like I appreciate you. Thank you Trevor. Nice to meet you Andrew. Thank you
Yeah, and so if it's really cool actually having a channel is that I get to help people
That I actually like on YouTube and so you know I've worked really hard. Hey, we've got you in the chat
What's up, Gotti? We are here with Andrew. He is a power lifter on YouTube and
Really good guy. Hopefully a new friend of the show and
Really a thrill to have on today. I have been watching for a couple months, and I like I like what I see
So thank you so much also for for your time and everything and chatting with us
I think that I think the chat really likes you and I'm sure you'll have some more people saying hi to you and you're in
your in your show and
Hopefully
Make your YouTube dreams come true
You have any if you have any any questions about YouTube ever, you know, hit me up any time too. I'm happy to happy to help you out on it
I've found some success here and happy to help other people. So yeah, so Goddy wants to know about what do you what are your thoughts about steroids?
I guess you're not you're all natural, right?
Yeah, so I've never taken anything who's blessed with some God-given genetics short arms
That helps me on the bench press stuff like that. No, but yeah, so if you're gonna use stairwise
Let's be honest most people so like if you're trying to think of your dream physique
And this is remember I'd say quote coach Greg do you set you talk about this if you're thinking about your dream
Oh, I want to look like Chris Bumstead
okay we'll cut that in half that should be your goal if you're a natural person
because obviously something like that is juicy and big time but like yeah if you
you should look at your goal physique and then you should be like all right
i'm gonna i realistically i think i get the half of that and it doesn't only matter
where you end up as long as you're you know having fun feeling like you're doing something
good for yourself it's good for your mind and stuff
Like yeah, just try to get in and train as much as possible. So about first steroids man
If you're not competing in bodybuilding have like a decently high level or if you're not competing in powerlifting and winning competitions at high level
I would just say don't do it. And if you are gonna start steroids, there's nothing wrong with steroids like I love watching strongman competitions
That's my favorite thing Brian Shaw Eddie Hall their deadlifting like 1100 pounds and shit like that
What the fuck but those guys are all juiced up. But basically what I'm saying is
at the absolute earliest and this of course comes with at least five years of training first natural
training wait till you're 25 yeah wait till your brain is fully developed they got these
Freaking taking steroids and they're still in there. They're still hitting puberty
Like that's gonna really fuck your shit up later on in life because your body's gonna think oh
I'm getting testosterone for here so your nuts are gonna be like all right
I'll go on vacation and then once you freaking get off this stuff your body can't produce its own natural testosterone
So you'll literally so how it works. You'll literally become a woman
Genetically not genetically
Hormonally for a little bit. So basically, I'm gonna throw my camera back on really quick. Basically when you take steroids, right?
Your testosterone goes up. So does your estrogen, right?
Normal man's like this higher testosterone estrogen takes their words and goes like this if you when you get off those steroids
We don't take something called a PCT a post-psychotherapy
Once your testosterone drops your estrogen will say hi and you'll become like a woman for a little bit
You know hormonally, so when you do get off I recommend taking a PCT so that it drops it at the same
You know it drops it like this like your testosterone levels or whatever
There's a I don't know. I've definitely watched a lot of
Stuff once you're into the industry like you know
you're gonna see things and and it's quite obvious the more you work out it's pretty obvious to figure
because somebody's on stairway they got a lot of acne their traps are humongous their quads are big
their voice is deep they got a lot of hair they're going bald it's pretty you know i saw some guy on
on a tiktok recently and like i saw his back and his back was just covered in the craters it was
Yeah, but it's like I mean if I was to take steroids I'd be afraid I'd lose my hair and I'd like you know
I'd like my balls would shrink up and you know
I think so and that's the other thing people don't realize with steroids like it's an enhancer
So you're looking at the best physics in the world
Well, guess what those guys have better genetics than I do naturally so like they're building on top of already you guys think I'm big
Me on steroids would be ridiculous, but like if you hopped on, not really dude. You look flabby. I'm walking a lot
I have trolls on the show too
What was I saying oh, yeah enhance the leg of here
Yeah, if you took steroids you just feel a little bigger than you are now, right you there's no possible way on planet Earth
You could ever look like my proportions with your no
Be my proportions at six foot three you'd have to weigh like 350 pounds you'd have to gain like 200 pounds
So it's like an enhancer people like those start the gym for a year. They're like, oh, I suck at this like 16 years old
Blah, that's like. Well, yeah, you're fucking 16 years old. You just started like you don't know
You don't know your genetics like and and hopping on steroids is not gonna. It's really not gonna do much and
Then I noticed I think that you already have good genetics like me or like I don't really need to again like I said
I'm actually gonna really compete or something like I just don't think it's worth it
Also, my wife would kill me if I took them so
Also, I don't have the money for that much. It's expensive
Yeah, but you don't do you don't do like a bodybuilding competitions you do power lift it
Do you do competes a power lifting competition? Well, I'm a person I compete with myself. I don't really
Do any of this competition. I would do okay
Let's be honest. I would do okay and like the high level stuff
But if I really wanted to hone in I'll definitely lose a little bit of the belly while trying to stay as strong as possible
Could I be putting like a 225 weight class?
Well, like so when's your are you gonna do a competition, but you only compete with yourself you say so it's like
No
But you're doing your channel. Yeah, and I almost have like a character. It's like it is it is not it's like different than just someone working out
It's like it's entertaining. It's uh, you're you're you're very funny and it's like you do have this like alter ego
That's like
You talk to you during this voice will come out the weird voice, you know, that's daddy business taking over
He's talking through me, but yeah, we like to get in there. We like to entertain sometimes you'll learn something
Sometimes we'll get motivated sometimes you'll laugh sometimes you'll
Sing well sometimes we sing and dance in there, but yeah
Nice, it's all good. I turn into what I have to to get done what I have to when I'm in there
But what it's all said and done me like to check back into reality. I don't want to stay evil
What do you do for like a living normally like you know, what's your normal career your electrician, okay?
Yeah, and it seems like you know
You've got a you got a lot of great equipment and stuff
And or how'd you do that? How'd you come across all that equipment? Like it seems like you have a lot of it
so
Let's see. So yeah, like a lot of it came from so when I first started lifting I worked at this one place
And the old boss was throwing out all these old plates and bars and because he's rich he's gonna buy new stuff
I was like very serious 45 pounds 45 pounds. I don't care what it looks like. So if I can snatch all that up
I probably got like 500 pounds from him
slowly then just acquiring
Stuff sometimes my parents will buy me something for my birthday or Christmas, but I got my point right now
I don't really need anything else
like I upgrade some of the stuff that I have but
Let's bless to have what I have. I don't really need anything else
Well, where is that you have this room? Is that your workout room? You have this one workout room or is your house getting overtaken by equipment?
That's all in the basement. It's all the base. Oh, that's your basement. Okay. Yeah
nice
Well, do you ever have friends come over and out and work out with you?
Yeah, my friends come over all the time. So I've been trying to get my friends to work out of it
They just don't like it
But I don't think they feel anything too crazy like I'd like to throw someone in the deep end
I threw myself into the deep end and said figure it out
But like that's not a great way to make somebody want to come back the next day. So yeah, they just
He's got working into their schedule. I'm always available. I don't care if you've never trained before or have a good time
Yeah, that'd be good to see like, you know people other people on the show to that because
Like on my channel
There's probably been at least nine or ten other dudes. I have been training with me. I think my sister even was in one of them
I don't know
Are your sister? Okay, cool
Like yeah, so that's it's always awesome to get other people involved and on the show too and maybe they could
They could I get inspired to so
Yeah, it's really awesome to talk to you like um, is there any message you have for or any uh, you know
Go ahead and shout out your show and tell everybody where to find you and how often you're on and stuff and get a good plug in
There's a daddy bigness on YouTube somehow that name wasn't taken so I took it and I'm not going to change it
But yeah, that's my thing you can follow me there. It's also my Instagram and Facebook
There I really don't care
But yeah message for the world. It doesn't really matter what happens last rep
I don't really care it really only matters what happens during the next rep because the last rep went bad
Well, you know, I better fucking figure it out
And sometimes you go in and it doesn't, it's not gonna be the best fucking day
Where you're gonna leave once things go hard or you're gonna fucking actually stay and at least go through the motions
That's that's what really determines a gym rat, a gym rat
That's almost unhealthily obsessed with the gym. I'm just like your average goer. Some people might go into the gym
They're like, oh
Touch the weights. I don't feel it today leave. Nah, it's not an option. I don't really care
And if you're not feeling it today, you slightly lighter weight or it doesn't matter
That's why bodybuilding is so easy
You can always have a good day even if you're sore because you're measuring it off of failure power lifting
It's tough. I know what I should be able to lift and if I go in there and I don't lift it
Like you know, you're gonna be a little bit upset. So and most days you are upset like 90% of the time you're in there
Especially when you're at the peak of your physique and strength you're basically peaked
Yeah, you're gonna be fucked, but we had a really good day in there today
Awesome
Hey, I wanted you to know you're you're welcome back anytime and uh, also like, you know a whole trevor's back
Let's see who trevor has in the question
Trevor
Ah
Okay, daddy bigness. I'm sorry. That was a porn bomb. I'm sorry daddy bigness. That was a great